<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    tools:context=".Bathroom">


    <androidx.cardview.widget.CardView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent"
        android:layout_marginTop="25dp"
        android:layout_marginLeft="15dp"
        android:layout_marginRight="15dp"
        android:layout_marginBottom="25dp"
        app:cardCornerRadius="15dp"
        >

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginTop="15dp"
            android:gravity="center_horizontal"
            android:text="INSTRUCTIONS for Emergency Service"
            android:textColor="#000000"
            android:textSize="16dp" />

        <ScrollView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="match_parent"
            android:layout_marginTop="65dp"
            android:background="@color/lightGray">

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="match_parent"
                android:layout_marginLeft="8dp"
                android:layout_marginTop="8dp"
                android:inputType="textMultiLine"
                android:padding="6dp"
                android:text="Step 1:- Save maximum four contact numbers of your relatives.\n\nStep 2:- Tap TRY IT button to test the functionality of the SOS.\n\nStep 3:- The app will send SMS with your live location to all four
numbers and make phone call to first number. The live location will not be a link, instead it will be longitude, latitude and the exact place wherever you are present, so that your relatives could take action even if they don't have internet connection.\n\nStep 4:- Now, Ladybuddy is ready to help you in emergency situations.\n\nLet's see how you will use ladybuddy in emergency:-\n\nStep 1:- Whenever you go through any unsafe place, just open the app and press back or home button so that the app starts running in the background.\n\nStep 2:- Make Sure that app is running in the background that means it is in the system tray.\n\nStep 3:- Whenever you feel emergency, tapping power button three times will send Emergency message and call, tapping it again three times will start a siren to deviate the culprit.\n\nStep 4:- Make Sure that all these 6 times tapping should be in one minute otherwise you will have to again start tapping count from zero.\n\nStep 5:- Tapping power button again three times or closing the app from background will stop the siren.\n\nNote:- Make sure that tapping power button means screen goes off or on"
                android:textColor="#000000"
                android:textSize="14sp" />
        </ScrollView>
    </androidx.cardview.widget.CardView>

</androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>